RIZKI IKHSAN RAMADHANI

Bandar Lampung, Lampung, 35229 | +62 899 3034 931 | rizki.ikhsan.ramadhani97@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/ikhsanrmdhn12

Executive Summary

I am a service oriented, dynamic and adaptive individual with a strong will to learn. Able to do team work and focus on solutions. GPA 3.60 at the University of Lampung. I have experience as a copywriter and consistently produce more than 350 articles and copies per month.

Skills and Competency

- Copywriting
- Creative Writing
- User Experience Writing
- Writing

- Proofreading
- Interpersonal skills
- Digital Marketing
- Communication skills

Work Experiences

Studio Design Portopath (Bandar Lampung, Indonesia)

Copywriter (December 2021 - June 2022)

- I created 90 articles and copies a week on mental health, beauty, and skincare to be used as infographics.
- Deliver the relevant writing tone and style in line with the specific demands.
- Research and analyze copywriting trends and other information related to mental health, beauty, and skincare campaigns.
- Proofread article contents and copies for grammar, spelling, and punctuation errors (English and Bahasa Indonesia).

Volunteering Experiences

AISEC UNILA (Bandar Lampung, Indonesia)

Local Volunteer Mahidana (January 2022 - February 2022)

- Raising awareness about climate change among young people in Bandar Lampung using social media.
- Through social media, we were able to successfully inform young people in Bandar Lampung about the consequences of the climate issue, food waste, and food loss.
- Accountable for watching, monitoring, and engaging in the green planting action day, as well as creating ecobricks around other participants.

AISEC UNILA (Bandar Lampung, Indonesia)

Local Volunteer Youth Entrepreneur Project (July 2019 – August 2019)

- I aid exchange participants with every activity while monitoring, evaluating, and mediating good communication between the local party and exchange participant.
- To improve space capacity, exchange participants and I explored ideas for renovating the BAM Coffee Shop's interior. while also discussed campaign strategy to promote them on Car free day.

Education Level

Universitas Lampung (2016-2022)

Bachelor Degree in Human Resource Management, 3.60/4.00

• Active as a Member of the Economic English club, Kelompok Studi Pasar Modal at college.

Achievements

Universitas Lampung (2016-2022)

Bachelor Degree in Human Resource Management, 3.60/4.00

- 1st Winner Stocklab Competition Sharia Capital Market Festival 2019
- 1st Winner Stocklab Competition KSPM Fair 2019